

Profile

I am a hardworking, determined, friendly and enthusiastic person. The various roles I have had have expanded and improved my ability to effectively communicate with children and adults alike. I have experience in different work environments and can adapt to new situations. Moreover, I pride myself in my ability organise my time effectively to ensure a task is completed to the best of my abilities.

Education

University of Essex 2016 - 2019

• Law degree: 2:1

Queensmead High School 2009 – 2016

- A Levels: Law, Spanish, History and AS level English Literature
- 12 GCSEs A*-B including English Language and Literature

Work Experience

English teacher (Vaughan Systems September 2021- July 2022)

- Tailoring lessons to each student's company/profession
- Writing reports based on student's progress
- Handling any IT problems as classes are online

English Language Assistant via British Council (CIEP Plurilingüe Isidro Parga Pondal Santa Cruz, October 2019– May 2021)

- Worked with other teachers and alone to plan lessons
- Adapted to working in an international environment
- Improved my ability to speak Spanish and my understanding of effective communication

English teacher (Os pitinos O Burgo Spain, October 2020-February 2021)

- Planned and delivered lessons for young children (aged 4-9)
- Enhanced my ability to think on the spot and react to new situations
- Gained confidence by presenting to a class of young children

English teacher (Speak English La Coruna, October 2019- June 2021)

- Delivered lessons to children and adults
- Ensured the classes were engaging, effective and suitable for each age group

• Set goals for students and guided them to achieve said goals

Cashier/Bartender/Front of house staff/Server (Appetite4work, June 2019 – September 2021)

Customer Service Assistant (Alice's Attic, June 2017 - September 2019) Cashier (McDonald's, March - September 2016)

- Worked in a team to achieve goals
- Actively listened to customers in need
- Worked in high pressure environments
- Dealt with customer complaints, solving problems
- Developed strategies to improve productivity

Voluntary Positions/Positions of Responsibility/ Achievements

Resident Assistant 2018-2019

- Developed a sense of community among the residents
- Organised events and projects to increase engagement
- Worked as a team with other RAs on projects
- Dealt with challenging situations

Silver Big Essex Award 2016-2019

Skills

- Competent in Microsoft Office Suite
- Proficient in Spanish

References available on request.